// EASY QUESTIONS
let easyStock = [{
    question: `How many bending elements are there?` ,
    answer: [`Two`,`Four`,`Six`,`Eight`],
    correctAnswer: `B`,
    value: 1000
},
{
    question: `Who is the last Airbender?`,
    answer: [`Aang`,`Korra`,`Uung`,`The Boulder`],
    correctAnswer: `A`,
    value: 1000
    },
{
    question: `What animal does Aang ride?`,
    answer: [`Lemur`, `Hog Monkey`, `Unagi`, `Flying Bison`],
    correctAnswer: `D`,
    value: 1000
    },
{
    question: `What weapon does Sokka carry?`,
    answer: [`net`,`boomerang`, `dagger`,`these hands`],
    correctAnswer: `B`,
    value: 1000
    },
{
    question: `What does Zuko need to regain?`,
    answer: [`lost lunch`, `money`, `honor`,`girlfriend`],
    correctAnswer: `C`,
    value: 1000
    },
{
    question: `Who is the Blue Spirit?`,
    answer: [`Iroh`,`Jet`,`Zuko`, `Momo`],
    correctAnswer: `C`,
    value: 1000
    },
{
    question: `Who is Zuko's uncle?`,
    answer: [`Nezuko`, `Rock Lee`, `Hama`, `Iroh`],
    correctAnswer: `D`,
    value: 1000
    },
{
    question: `Can Sokka bend any elements?`,
    answer: [`No`, `Yes`, `What is bending?`, `Only when he has a sword`],
    correctAnswer: `A`,
    value: 1000
    },
{
    question: `Where is Azula from?`,
    answer: [`Earth Kingdom`, `The Swamp`, `Fire Nation`, `The Northern Air Temple`],
    correctAnswer: `C`,
    value: 1000
    },
{
    question: `Bonus: What does Sifu Mike wear on Friday's?`,
    answer: [`tropical shirt`, `gi`, `Gucci slides`,`straw hat`],
    correctAnswer: `A`,
    value: 25250
    },
]
// MEDIUM QUESTIONS
let mediumStock = [
    {
        question: `What is Iroh's nick name?`,
        answer: [`The Dragon of the West`, `The Sleeping Bison`,`A Chattering Hog Monkey`,`The Tsungi God`],
        correctAnswer: `A`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `Who was the Firelord before Ozai?`,
        answer: [`Kyoshi`,`Jeung Jeung`, `Roku`,`Azulon`],
        correctAnswer: `D`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `Sokkas first girlfriend is?`,
        answer: [`Katara`, `Toph`,`Yue`,`Suki`],
        correctAnswer: `C`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `How many years was Aang frozen for?`,
        answer: [10,80,90,100],
        correctAnswer: `D`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `When is all Firebending "turned off"?`,
        answer: [`Summer Solstice`, `Equinox`, `During an eclipse`, `Lunar Eclipse`],
        correctAnswer: `C`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `What kind of bending does Aang learn from the Lion Turtle?`,
        answer: [`Water bending`, `Energy bending`,`Light bending`, `Tear bending`],
        correctAnswer: `B`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `What is Iroh obssessed with?`,
        answer: [`Crackers`, `Coffee`,`Tea`, `Water`],
        correctAnswer: `C`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `Who were the original Earth benders?`,
        answer: [`Badgermoles`,`Catpigs`,`Tigerdillos`, `Raptoreagles`],
        correctAnswer: `A`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `What was hidden in the dessert?`,
        answer: [`The Oasis,`,`Wan Shi Tongs Libary`,`The Spirit World`,`The Northern Air Temple`],
        correctAnswer: `B`,
        value: 10000
        },
    {
        question: `Bonus: What is this number? 10101 `,
        answer: [24,21,23,20],
        correctAnswer: `B`,
        value: 25250
        },
]
// HARD QUESTIONS
let hardStock = [
    {
        question: `Who is Piando?`,
        answer: [`craftsman`, `black smith`, `sword smith`,`fisherman`],
        correctAnswer: `C`,
        value: 25000
        },
    {
        question: `Who is a member of the white lotus?`,
        answer: [`Zhaire`,`Bumi`,`Gyatso`,`Genji`],
        correctAnswer: `B`,
        value: 25000
         },
    {
        question: `Who said the quote in the beginning of this quiz?`,
        answer: [`Iroh`, `Combustion Man`, `Roku`, `Tarloq`],
        correctAnswer: `A`,
        value: 25000
        },
    {
        question: `What is the Avatar the bridge of?`,
        answer: [`The Economy and Classism`, `The Spirit World and Humans`, `The Great Divide`, `The North and South Poles`],
        correctAnswer: `B`,
        value: 25000
        },
    {
        question: `What is Hei Bei?`,
        answer: [`demon`, `parrot`, `panda`, `Sand bender`],
        correctAnswer: `C`,
        value: 25000
        },
    {
        question: `Who is Zuko's great grant father from his mother's side? `,
        answer: [`Zhao`, `Roku`, `Bumi`,`Kurok`],
        correctAnswer: `B`,
        value: 25000
        },
    {
        question: `Until what age did Avatar Kyoshi live?`,
        answer: [200,320,230,130],
        correctAnswer: `C`,
        value: 25000
        },
    {
        question: `Who commanded the Dai Li before Azula?`,
        answer: [`Long Feng`, `Toph Beifong`, `Han`, `Koh`],
        correctAnswer: `A`,
        value: 25000
        },
    {
        question: `Who is the face stealer?`,
        answer: [`Piando`,`Koh`,`Rava`,`Koizilla`],
        correctAnswer: `B`,
        value: 25000
        },
    {
        question: `Bonus: When was Ironhack founded?`,
        answer: [2015,2016,2014,2013],
        correctAnswer: `D`,
        value: 50000
        },
]
// Trivia questions end -----------------------------------------
